Health insurance, which you
can genuinely avail, has slabs of every kind. The
more policies you sell in the G slab,
the higher the slab you will receive.
Plus will
come.
[Music]
[Applause]
Hello friends, how are you? I hope you are
well and all is well in the family.
Friends, we believe in providing general public with excellent opportunities
in different working areas in the insurance segment.
Today I have brought another wonderful and short story for you:
How to become an agent at Tata Egg.
Tata Egg, as you know by name, is one of the
best companies and the Tata Egg Group is a great company in its own way.
Both have a joint
collaboration and everyone
knows Tata Egg very well in India.
Tata Egg is available in the health segment, i.e., the health
insurance business.
Here
you can do all three segments simultaneously. With a single
code, you can sell health insurance,
you can sell motor insurance,
you can sell non-motor insurance. Friends, it
is so big and so amazing that you might
not believe it. Why am I saying this?
Because many people think that
Tata Egg  Joining a company like this as an agent,
advisor or consultant would be very difficult.
How would you join? Genuinely friends, it
is difficult, but I have made this difficulty easy
for you and for all those
people who are looking for a business opportunity, are
looking for an opportunity
that can be done along with business or full
time as a career. There is an
opportunity working in the health insurance business which you
can avail. Yes friends, here
in Tata Egg, three jobs are available under a single code in
which you can work and the health
insurance segment itself is a very big
genuine segment as you all
know, in the Covid scenario, everyone has become
aware that health
insurance is very important and you must also
know that treatment in a cash hospital is
very expensive, but
if you have health insurance then your
treatment becomes really free and cashless and
when I talk about Tata Egg's health insurance, then
here it becomes extra incomplete, it is
extreme, it becomes self-free,
here not even a single pen is paid to the customer.
This is amazing in itself.
Actually, it is 100% cashless and
if I talk about it in all the policies of Tata, then
generally this feature is available. So
friends, let me try to understand this career opportunity
in a little detail.
First, let me
tell you its positives or why the positives are so big
because the commission income that you get here,
what kind of salary you get in the company, the
less you do here, the more money
you will earn, that is, there is no limit, the
more policies you sell, the
more you can earn. And if I
talk about the payout structure, then the
payout ranges from 15% to 35%.
In health insurance, which you can genuinely
avail, there are slabs for every scheme.
The more policies you sell in the G slab,
the higher the salary you will
get. Plus, there are international and domestic
trips which you can avail.
This working will be available in every scheme, every quarter
and the early contact will be different. The
clubs for the whole year will be different.  So that you can
achieve those clubs of flood and also do
international and domestic business,
I told this in the big section of the health segment,
similarly when you join motor insurance and
earn for motor insurance with a
single code, then you can get payouts ranging from 2.5% to 25%
there, similarly when
you talk about non-motor, then you will get payouts ranging from 15% to
30% there as well
and here you
can sell in travel insurance which
is available at a commission ranging from 15% to 40%, friends,
this sir portfolio is available with a single code
for which you have to give an exam
and the exam fee is ₹700,
this is the list of documents,
you have to send this document to me on WhatsApp,
each document in it,
not a single document will be missing in it, keep this in mind, plus a
fee of 700 will be charged, this is for those people
who want to earn general, I apologize to
all those people who are
taking the code just for timepass or  If you want to
take a code only for motor insurance, then
I apologize for them because our
segment is the health insurance segment.
Along with health, you can do other things as well,
motor and non-motor. It is
necessary for you to do health as well and for this there
is a mandatory condition as well. It is necessary to take a minimum health policy in a year
and the
minimum premium of one policy should be
₹15000. If you do a policy of ₹60000 in a year, then
your
code will always be active and there will be
no problem of any kind. After getting the first policy code,
you have to do it within a week or 10 days. It has to be done
in the first month. It is mandatory
because the purpose of taking the code is to reduce the
time and not to pass it. We train all our
agents to earn at least ₹2 lakh to ₹10 lakh in a year
on full working and many
agents are earning ₹500000000 a year.
If you are also a big name in this field, you can earn big
money along with active income.  If you
want to earn income, you will have money even if you reduce it and even if you do
not reduce it, you will have money. For that,
you will have to give 5 years in the industry. You will have to take out
time in this industry and
sell maximum number of policies.
We work on the same simple formula.
Send 100-100 policies in a year. You
also need 500
policies in 5 years. If your minimum average is 100, then you can go for it. If the policies are worth
20 lakhs in 1 year, then it will become worth
one crore in 5 years. And after 5 years, even if
you stop reducing, you will still get an
income of 15 lakhs throughout your life. If you want to achieve
something big in your industry, your life
and want my annual
fixed income pension income to become ₹15 lakhs, then
give 5 years to this industry. I
promise you, I guarantee you.
If you spare one hour daily or even just
reduce Saturdays and Sundays, then it can easily be
good.
We do all its detailed training in Zoom sessions,
completely on the digital platform, friends.
You
can join us digitally, no matter where you are in India. You don't need to be enrolled in any branch. You just have to appear for the
exam once.
We will share the material for the ₹700 fee.
Taking the ID exam is
mandatory for anyone with a life insurance agency or health insurance agency. Therefore, I am explaining to you the
fee of ₹700. You have to
pay it to us only then your exam will be scheduled.
This will take 10 to 12 days. Let's
talk about it, friends.
Apart from this payout, you get rewards and recognition
in domestic and international tours.
Many achievers visit us
regularly and enjoy Tata's tours.
You can go alone or with your
family. The
more you earn, the more tickets
you can qualify for. Plus, let me talk about the
biggest benefit of joining this profession. This is a noble profession, where
people here  That you generally help,
here
we do not believe in any kind of financial activity and the
entire money comes after TDS deduction,
which will enhance your lifestyle,
people will know you well
and you will also become famous, if you
want to earn big then friends this
platform is available only for you,
in this Devna, those people who are
interested in this business, this opportunity, want to join, want to
learn, want to earn, then all those
people can write to me on WhatsApp,
how to become a Tata Egg Agent, you will have
a virtual interview with us,
without virtual interview we do
not process anything and
in that virtual interview it will be confirmed that whatever
you have done, this is its minimum condition,
you will fulfill it, you will
login in the first month only then we will
process your code after your confirmation
and my simple request is if you have
4 pulses in a year, nothing happens
friends, in a year people earn 100, 200,
500  Let's talk about versus selling, you can buy 50%
but 4% is the minimum, so friends, this
positive is genuinely available for you, do
n't be afraid of it, grab it today itself, General,
Namaskar to you friend Yogendra Verma, don't forget to
subscribe to my channel, share it, comment,
this is very important for you,
if you want the latest information, Namaskar
[Sangeet]